by RentAnAdviser.com
If I woke up without ya
I don′t know what I would do
Thought I could be single forever
′Til I met you
Usually‚ don′t be fallin′‚
be fallin′ fallin′ fast
You gotta way of keeping
me comin′ back to back
I just found out‚ the only reason
that you lovin′ me
Was to get back at your ex lover
but before you leave
Usually‚ I would never‚
would never even care
Baby I know she creepin′‚
I feel it in the air
Every night and every day
I try to make you stay
But your
Savage love
Did somebody‚ did somebody
Break your heart?
Lookin′ like an angel
But your savage love
When you kiss me
I know you don′t give two fucks
But I still want that
Your savage love
Your savage love love love
You could use me
Cause I still want that your savage
Baby‚ I hope that this ain′t
karma cause I get around
You wanna run it up‚ I
wanna lock it down
Usually‚ don′t be fallin′‚
be fallin′ fallin′ fast
You gotta way of making me
spend up all my cash
Every night and every day (Every day)
I try to make you stay
But your
Savage love
Did somebody‚ did somebody
Break your heart?
Lookin′ like an angel
But your savage love
When you kiss me
I know you don′t give two fucks
But I still want that
Your savage love
Your savage love love love
You could use me
Cause I still want that
your savage love
Your savage love love love
You could use me
Baby
Savage love
Did somebody‚ did somebody
Break your heart?
Lookin′ like an angel
But your savage love
When you kiss me
I know you don′t give two fucks
But I still want that
Your savage love (savage love)
Your savage love love love
Girl you could use me
Cause I still want that
your savage love
by RentAnAdviser.com